TRISTEN ABELLA

Brentwood, CA • (408) 823-4418 • tristenabella@gmail.com

SUMMARY

Support technician with three years of experience handling various hardware and software of audiovisual and IT equipment. Dependable and hard-working team player with the ability to effectively communicate technical issues to customers and provide excellent customer service. Has a growth mindset that can quickly learn and apply existing and new technologies.

SKILLS

- Can troubleshoot desktop, laptop, and mobile device hardware and software issues
- Can support Windows 8 and 10 OS, Mac OS, and Microsoft Office 365
- Familiarized with Group Policy and Active Directory
- Knowledgeable on networking concepts such as DNS, DHCP, TCP/IP, LAN, WAN, VPN, RDP, VoIP

CERTIFICATIONS

- CompTIA A+ CE Certification
- CompTIA Network+ CE Certification

EXPERIENCE

Field Support Technician

February 2021 – Current

Worldwide TechServices LLC. Pleasanton, CA

- Call customers over the phone and provide timely break/fix support for Dell, Lenovo, and HP desktops and laptops throughout Pleasanton and surrounding areas
- Troubleshoot desktop and laptop issues
- Configure BIOS and run diagnostics to ensure functionality of desktops and laptops
- Deliver all service calls assigned, continuously satisfying various customers

Audio Visual Technician

July 2019 – March 2020

Encore Technologies (Formerly PSAV), Palo Alto, CA

- Collaborated with fellow technicians to setup, operate, and dismantle audiovisual equipment and laptops for corporate meetings and conferences throughout the Crowne Plaza Hotel in a timely and attentive manner
- Assisted corporate events and conventions alongside technicians at various hotel locations, continuously satisfying various clients, such as Stanford and Intuit, of all their audiovisual needs
- Exceeded expectations of internal and external customers

Audio Visual Technician

February 2018 - June 2019

Associated Students of San Francisco State University, San Francisco, CA

- Learned to setup, operate, and dismantle audiovisual equipment for school events, meetings, and musical concerts throughout campus
- Learned the importance of excellent customer service
- Continuously satisfied all event needs of clients for their school events

EDUCATION

Bachelor of Arts in Broadcast & Electronic Communication Arts

May 2019

San Francisco State University, San Francisco, CA

• Core subjects focused on the operation of media production hardware and software, as well as the communication, research, and writing of electronic media